Louis Simpson Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Subject File, 1922-2011 (Box 189-212)
  - Travel (Box 209)
    - Australia, 1979-1980, (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box 210)
    - France, 1948-1949, 1975, (2 folders) (Box 210)
    - Italy and France, 1973, (2 folders) (Box 210)
    - Italy, 1982 (Box 210)
    - Romania, 1996, (2 folders) (Box 211)
    - Sweden, 1998, (2 folders) (Box 211)
  - U.S. Army, circa 1945, 1989, (2 folders) (Box 211)
  - Van Doren, Mark, 1970-1972, 1995 See also Container 17, Van Doren, Mark (Box 212)
  - Vaughan, Robert, 1991-1998, (2 folders) (Box 212)
  - Whitman, Walt, 1969, 1982, undated See also Oversize (Box 212)
  - Writing tips and techniques, undated (Box 212)
- Oversize, 1982 (Box OV 1)
  Poetry reading poster, and a woodcut-print portrait of Walt Whitman created by Mark Nuccio.
  Arranged and described according to the series, containers, and folders from which the items were removed.
  - Professional file
    - Poetry reading poster, undated (Container 168, Engagements) (Box OV 1)
  - Subject file
    - Walt Whitman woodcut-print portrait by Mark Nuccio, 1982 (Container 212, Walt Whitman) (Box OV 1)